{"agefgaesgae":{"username":"agefgaesgae","assessmentData":[]},"gaegag":{"username":"gaegag","assessmentData":[{"questions":[{"question":"I am only relaxed when I have total control over my life.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"Thinking about what I’ve done the past few months felt unenjoyable.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I often pretend to believe certain things so I can \"fit in.\"","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"When speaking to others, I generally don't talk about myself in a positive way.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I avoid talking about my culture because people might think it is weird.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I have stopped doing things I used to enjoy.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"Recently I have been on guard, watchful, or easily startled.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":true},{"question":"It has been hard finding motivation to do schoolwork, chores, or daily activities.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"It has been easy to lose my appetite and I have been eating less than usual.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"It has been difficult to enjoy daily activities or routines.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I have been feeling disconnected from friends, family, or colleagues.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I feel unwelcome and/or uncomfortable in social situations because of my culture or background.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I feel like I don't \"fit in.\" because my culture or background is different from others'.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I often feel the need to hide my culture or parts of my identity.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I have been experiencing moments of racing thoughts and restlessness that I find difficult to control.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":true},{"question":"I frequently worry about the future of various aspects of my life, such as work, relationships, or health.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I do not feel satisfied with my overall well-being.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I do not regularly spend time pursuing my hobbies and doing things I enjoy.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I find it hard to relax and wind down.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"My daily responsibilities, activities, or interactions feel overwhelming.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I sleep less than I normally do.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I have too manny commitments (work, school, clubs, extracurriculars, etc.).","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I have recently been experiencing nightmares or distressing dreams.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":true},{"question":"I often feel on edge or easily startled, even in non-threatening situations.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":null},{"question":"I have recently experienced bad major changes in my life and/or relationships.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":1,"user_response":null},{"question":"I am rarely congragulated or encouraged by my friends or family.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":null},{"question":"I am not confident about how I look and how other people see me.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I am very hesitant to try things and doubt my abilities.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true}],"date":"Sun Nov 26 2023 16:42:41 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time)"}]},"efsf":{"username":"efsf","assessmentData":[]},"sef":{"username":"sef","assessmentData":[]},"wfefewf":{"username":"wfefewf","assessmentData":[]},"efsfszf":{"username":"efsfszf","assessmentData":[]},"dashsa":{"username":"dashsa","assessmentData":[]},"fdsdsfs":{"username":"fdsdsfs","assessmentData":[]},"fsdfsd":{"username":"fsdfsd","assessmentData":[{"questions":[{"question":"I am only relaxed when I have total control over my life.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"Thinking about what I’ve done the past few months felt unenjoyable.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I often pretend to believe certain things so I can \"fit in.\"","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"When speaking to others, I generally don't talk about myself in a positive way.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I avoid talking about my culture because people might think it is weird.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have stopped doing things I used to enjoy.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"Recently I have been on guard, watchful, or easily startled.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"It has been hard finding motivation to do schoolwork, chores, or daily activities.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"It has been easy to lose my appetite and I have been eating less than usual.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"It has been difficult to enjoy daily activities or routines.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have been feeling disconnected from friends, family, or colleagues.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I feel unwelcome and/or uncomfortable in social situations because of my culture or background.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I feel like I don't \"fit in.\" because my culture or background is different from others'.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I often feel the need to hide my culture or parts of my identity.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have been experiencing moments of racing thoughts and restlessness that I find difficult to control.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I frequently worry about the future of various aspects of my life, such as work, relationships, or health.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I do not feel satisfied with my overall well-being.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I do not regularly spend time pursuing my hobbies and doing things I enjoy.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I find it hard to relax and wind down.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"My daily responsibilities, activities, or interactions feel overwhelming.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I sleep less than I normally do.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have too manny commitments (work, school, clubs, extracurriculars, etc.).","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have recently been experiencing nightmares or distressing dreams.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I often feel on edge or easily startled, even in non-threatening situations.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have recently experienced bad major changes in my life and/or relationships.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am rarely congragulated or encouraged by my friends or family.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am not confident about how I look and how other people see me.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am very hesitant to try things and doubt my abilities.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false}],"date":"Tue Nov 28 2023 16:54:57 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time)"},{"questions":[{"question":"I am only relaxed when I have total control over my life.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"Thinking about what I’ve done the past few months felt unenjoyable.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I often pretend to believe certain things so I can \"fit in.\"","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"When speaking to others, I generally don't talk about myself in a positive way.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I avoid talking about my culture because people might think it is weird.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have stopped doing things I used to enjoy.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"Recently I have been on guard, watchful, or easily startled.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"It has been hard finding motivation to do schoolwork, chores, or daily activities.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"It has been easy to lose my appetite and I have been eating less than usual.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"It has been difficult to enjoy daily activities or routines.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have been feeling disconnected from friends, family, or colleagues.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I feel unwelcome and/or uncomfortable in social situations because of my culture or background.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I feel like I don't \"fit in.\" because my culture or background is different from others'.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I often feel the need to hide my culture or parts of my identity.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have been experiencing moments of racing thoughts and restlessness that I find difficult to control.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I frequently worry about the future of various aspects of my life, such as work, relationships, or health.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I do not feel satisfied with my overall well-being.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I do not regularly spend time pursuing my hobbies and doing things I enjoy.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I find it hard to relax and wind down.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"My daily responsibilities, activities, or interactions feel overwhelming.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I sleep less than I normally do.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have too manny commitments (work, school, clubs, extracurriculars, etc.).","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have recently been experiencing nightmares or distressing dreams.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I often feel on edge or easily startled, even in non-threatening situations.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have recently experienced bad major changes in my life and/or relationships.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am rarely congragulated or encouraged by my friends or family.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am not confident about how I look and how other people see me.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am very hesitant to try things and doubt my abilities.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false}],"date":"Tue Nov 28 2023 16:55:09 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time)"},{"questions":[{"question":"I am only relaxed when I have total control over my life.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"Thinking about what I’ve done the past few months felt unenjoyable.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I often pretend to believe certain things so I can \"fit in.\"","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"When speaking to others, I generally don't talk about myself in a positive way.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I avoid talking about my culture because people might think it is weird.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have stopped doing things I used to enjoy.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"Recently I have been on guard, watchful, or easily startled.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"It has been hard finding motivation to do schoolwork, chores, or daily activities.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"It has been easy to lose my appetite and I have been eating less than usual.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"It has been difficult to enjoy daily activities or routines.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have been feeling disconnected from friends, family, or colleagues.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I feel unwelcome and/or uncomfortable in social situations because of my culture or background.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I feel like I don't \"fit in.\" because my culture or background is different from others'.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I often feel the need to hide my culture or parts of my identity.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have been experiencing moments of racing thoughts and restlessness that I find difficult to control.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I frequently worry about the future of various aspects of my life, such as work, relationships, or health.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I do not feel satisfied with my overall well-being.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I do not regularly spend time pursuing my hobbies and doing things I enjoy.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I find it hard to relax and wind down.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"My daily responsibilities, activities, or interactions feel overwhelming.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I sleep less than I normally do.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have too manny commitments (work, school, clubs, extracurriculars, etc.).","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have recently been experiencing nightmares or distressing dreams.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I often feel on edge or easily startled, even in non-threatening situations.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have recently experienced bad major changes in my life and/or relationships.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am rarely congragulated or encouraged by my friends or family.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am not confident about how I look and how other people see me.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am very hesitant to try things and doubt my abilities.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false}],"date":"Tue Nov 28 2023 16:57:10 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time)"}]},"dsad":{"username":"dsad","assessmentData":[]},"das":{"username":"das","assessmentData":[]},"sdasd":{"username":"sdasd","assessmentData":[]},"fds":{"username":"fds","assessmentData":[]},"fdsjfs":{"username":"fdsjfs","assessmentData":[]},"dsd":{"username":"dsd","assessmentData":[]},"dsa":{"username":"dsa","assessmentData":[]},"fsdfs":{"username":"fsdfs","assessmentData":[]},"dasda":{"username":"dasda","assessmentData":[]},"":{"username":"","assessmentData":[]},"fddsd":{"username":"fddsd","assessmentData":[]},"fsdf":{"username":"fsdf","assessmentData":[]},"dasddasda":{"username":"dasddasda","assessmentData":[]},"sdf":{"username":"sdf","assessmentData":[]},"dsjbas":{"username":"dsjbas","assessmentData":[]},"dssd":{"username":"dssd","assessmentData":[]},"dsjfsjss":{"username":"dsjfsjss","assessmentData":[]},"dsaadasd":{"username":"dsaadasd","assessmentData":[]},"dsfsds":{"username":"dsfsds","assessmentData":[]},"dsfsd":{"username":"dsfsd","assessmentData":[]},"xccx":{"username":"xccx","assessmentData":[]},"cdsc":{"username":"cdsc","assessmentData":[]},"sdds":{"username":"sdds","assessmentData":[]},"asdasd":{"username":"asdasd","assessmentData":[]},"sda":{"username":"sda","assessmentData":[]},"sad":{"username":"sad","assessmentData":[]},"ads":{"username":"ads","assessmentData":[]}," ,m,m":{"username":" ,m,m","assessmentData":[]},"knl":{"username":"knl","assessmentData":[]},"Boris Boyanov Tomov":{"username":"Boris Boyanov Tomov","assessmentData":[]}}